Harry

Senior UX/UI and Product Designer

\(+9509428310392

I am digital product designers with 5 years experiences on digital product development. And my goal since my teenage is to make digital products to help people's life more easier and efficient. My Slogan is "I Design Products With Love".

Career History

Senior UX Designer @ Lexagle / Singapore

October 2022 - April 2023

 I own obligation management feature, public link to streamline contract inquiries. I collaborate with UI Designers Product Managers and Developers

Outcomes • Features are delivered to developers

UX Designer @ Treedots / Singapore

November 2021 - October 2022

- I took ownership on Supplier Portal for B2B Business Arm by collaborating together with Product Managers and Developers. Features that I design includes Sales Management, Order Management, Inventory Management, Dispute Management and so on.
- I also assist our Team Lead in building a remote-friendly work environment by leading activities like Good Vibe Fridays, fostering a strong Team
- I volunteered in addressing UX Debts in the system and solve by conducting user research, creating sitemaps, user flows, prototypes, design systems and usability testings, setting UX Metrics.

Outcomes

- Product is lunched into the market
- Successfully build remote friendly and collaborative design team
- Tracking UX Debt Plan is settled and most of them are solved.

Product Designer @ Nexlabs / Yangon

September 2020 - November 2021

 I collaborated with the design team, developers and business analysts in order to create design for diverse industries requested by clients. I design mobile and website products for FinTech, HealthTech, Entertainment and Community Based Non-Profit Organizations.

Outcomes: More than 5 digital products including mobile application, website and web applications are delivered into the market.

Career History Cont'd

UI/UX Designers @ Adventsoft / Yangon

December 2018 - September 2022

 I transitioned from a Software Engineer to a UI/UX Designer. My main responsibility is to design mobile and website products for FinTech, TeleHealth, E Commerces, Ride Hailing Platform, Insurances and Education Industries.

Outcomes: More than 10 digital products including mobile application, website and web applications are delivered into the market.

Internship @ Acroquests / Yangon

2018

• During the final year of my university, I worked as an internship. My responsibility is to create web application with Spring Boot.

Outcomes: I understood how the digital products are developed in the industry and hands on **experiences** with Software Development Life Circle.

Educations

Computer Sciences Degree @ University of Computer Studies, Taunggyi

2013 - 2018

• I learn about Computer Science, Human-Computer Interaction, Cyber Security, Software Engineering and Project Management.

Honorable **Mentions**

Speaker @ UXMM Events / Yangon

(2023)

In this event, I contributed the community about UX Debts and strategies about how to solve them.

Speaker @ Google DevCon / Yangon

(2022)

In this event, I contributed the community about the collaboration best practices between developers and designers

Skills

Tools

Figma, Figjam, Adobe CC, Sketch, Whimsicals, Notion, Maze, Protopie, Microsift Office, Google Workspace, HTML, CSS

Hard Skills

Wireframing, Rapid Prototyping, Design Research, Affinity Mapping , Workshop Ideation , Project Management , Accessibility , User Research, Design System, UX Debts Management

Soft Skills

Effective Communication, Leadership, Problem Solving, Crictical Thinking, People & Stakeholder Management

Certifications

Enterprise Design System - Co Creator (IBM)

Enterprise Design System - Practioner (IBM)

Product Management (Great Learning)

Introduction To Design Thinking (Great Learning)

Team Essential For AI (Great Learning)

Other Activities

Founder @ Design Matters

2022

 I started the local design community with my colleague from Treedots. Our goal is to help the designers find the path in the industry and grow as much as they can as a designer. We host activities like Sunday Talk where we discuss about different design topics with the designers and learn together from different perspectives.

Outcomes: We have more than 1K member in our community

who already are designers and who are interested

in the field.

Organizer @ Knowledge Bag Event

2020

 As I would like to contributed back to my university, I hosted the event called "Knowledge Bag" in which the alumni of the university contribute our industry knowledge back to the students from the university.

Outcomes: 80 % of the student from University of Computer

Studies, Taunggyi attended our event.

Strong Points

Understand both design and development steps, Always keen to contribute knowledge, Thinking out of the box, Research Based Design, Team Player, Universal Design

It is really hard to describe about me within two pages in resume. I have more stories to tell.

Please visit my Portfolio Website to Learn More.

- **4** +95 09 428 310 392
- https://kaungmyathein.github.io/harry.github.io/index.html
- in http://www.linkedin.com/in/kaung-myat-hein-harry
- M https://medium.com/@kaungmyat9702

